worldusabilityday.org 2012-12-30

# Privacy Policy | World Usability Day

The Usability Professionals Association (UPA) have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the web site [www.worldusabilityday.org](http://www.worldusabilityday.org/ "www.worldusabilityday.org").

## Personal Information

The registration form requires visitors to give us contact information (like their name and email address) when registering as a volunteer/supporter/sponsor.

Visitors' contact information is used to contact the visitors when necessary.

The UPA does not rent, sell, or give away mailing addresses, email addresses, telephone numbers, or fax numbers for members or visitors. However, we do reserve the right to release this information to the coordinating team for World Usability Day 2006,2007 and 2008.

Our online surveys ask visitors for contact information (like their email address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). Personal information from surveys will not be shared with anyone. Contact information from a survey will be used only to answer direct questions or respond to complaints. Most surveys are anonymous, and contact information is always optional.

## Links to Other Sites

This site contains links to other sites. The UPA is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

## Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Online access to membership records, including address information, is available to the UPA, and is password-protected.

Physical and network access to our web server is handled by [OHO](http://www.oho.com/).

## Choice/Opt-Out

This site gives members the following options for removing their information from the mailing/contact list. The same contacts can be used to change or modify information previously provided.

  * You can send email to [upa-board-wud@usabilityprofessionals.org](mailto:upa-board-wud@usabilityprofessionals.org).
  * You can send mail to the following postal address:   

140 N. Bloomingdale Road

Bloomingdale, IL 60108-1017

  * You can call the following telephone number: +1 630-980-4997
  * You can send a fax to: +1 630-351-8490

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact the UPA at the address below.
